♪ 相思难逃 ♪
200米后左转
♪ 别将西风落下 ♪
即将左转转头
不带左转
一边那半边无际
♪ Let me dance the night ♪
For change
Just wanna c
♪ For the candles seems of dpress bu ♪
摇摆250米后
在道路尽头左转1down
♪ For the crowding ♪
♪ 记忆知道那when before the safeday ♪
♪ You will lose me ♪
♪ You will for the postic come back ♪
If it still not too high
♪ I just wanna b ♪
红灯即将变绿
♪ For they cannot be the congress ♪
♪ 来不掉所有人的bi ♪
Don't mind
100分
继续行驶7km海
♪ A centre beautiful beachgoes far away ♪
The sn time fe my love
♪ You can't forget the worst cu ♪
♪ See you always time to fe ♪
吹的偏偏
♪ Left the sorrow ♪
♪ There's no winter ♪
♪ Sadness be demine full of broken hearthe people bodionnot ♪
♪ So around the su to the mind ♪
♪ The fbo ♪
I still hear your voice
When you sleep next to me
I still feel your touch in my lady
♪ My forgive me my witness ♪
♪ But i don't know why without you ♪
♪ It's hard to survive ♪
♪ Cause every time we touch ♪
♪ I get this feeling ♪
♪ And every time we kiss ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ I could slide ♪
♪ Can't you feel my heart be survise ♪
♪ Need you by my side ♪
♪ Cause every time we touch ♪
♪ I feel the stati ♪
♪ So i can't let you go want you in my life ♪
请沿沽河大堤右岸继续行驶4.5km
♪ Your arms are my castle ♪
Your heart is my sky
♪ They wipe the wait tears that i cry ♪
♪ The good ♪
♪ And the bad times ♪
♪ We've been through the wa ♪
You made me right when i f cause every time we touch i get this feeling
Cause every time we kiss i swear
♪ I could fly ♪
Can't you feel my heart beat fast
♪ I want this allai ♪
Need you by my side
♪ Cause every time we touch ♪
♪ I feel the started and every time we kiss ♪
I reach for the sky
♪ Can't you hear my heart beats ♪
So i can't let you go
♪ Want you in my life ♪
♪ Cause every time we touchi ♪
♪ Get this feeling ♪
And every time we kill
♪ Class need you by my side ♪
兰亭临帖行书如行
云流水月下门推心细如你脚步碎月
♪ 让不迭 ♪
♪ 千年碑 ♪
♪ 易拓却难拓你的美 ♪
曾几却走进个谁
♪ 牧笛横吹黄酒 ♪
♪ 小菜又几碟 ♪
♪ 夕阳余晖 ♪
♪ 如你的羞怯似醉 ♪
♪ 摹本易写而墨香不退 ♪
♪ 与你同留余味 ♪
♪ 一口朱砂到底圈了谁 ♪
♪ 泪无关 ♪
♪ 风月我题序 ♪
♪ 等你回海 ♪
♪ 悬笔一绝 ♪
♪ 那岸边浪千叠 ♪
♪ 情字何解 ♪
怎落笔都不对
♪ 而我独缺你一生的了解 ♪
呜大公园老人进了
你保持右侧天神秘人
我不追你了
有什么了解
情字不见任何人
独作碧苍
了解弹指
♪ 岁月倾城 ♪
♪ 顷刻间湮灭 ♪
♪ 青石板街 ♪
♪ 回眸一笑 ♪
♪ 你满月分了没 ♪
♪ 你要同情弹脆 ♪
♪ 让你错觉 ♪
♪ 眉夜鹤声归酒又无滋味 ♪
♪ 人雁南飞 ♪
♪ 转身一瞥 ♪
你噙泪
举一把年手揽回忆
♪ 怎么睡又怎么会心事 ♪
♪ 密缝绣花鞋 ♪
♪ 针针怨怼 ♪
♪ 若花怨蝶 ♪
♪ 你会怨着谁 ♪
♪ 泪无关 ♪
风月我题序
♪ 等你回 ♪
♪ 悬笔一绝 ♪
♪ 那岸边浪千叠 ♪
♪ 情字何解 ♪
♪ 怎落笔都不对 ♪
而我独缺你一生的了解
♪ 无关风月 ♪
♪ 我题序 ♪
♪ 等你回手 ♪
♪ 书无愧 ♪
400米后
在红绿灯路口左转
♪ 雨的摇曳又潇潇了几夜 ♪
♪ 我等着泪来提醒你爱谁 ♪
即将在红绿灯路口左转
左转
完整个夏天
伤并没有好一些
开着行驶在同
面有离开自己的
♪ 唱不完一首歌 ♪
疲倦还剩下黑眼圈
眼前的世界伤害在夜色难免
天黄昏再美
♪ 终要黑夜 ♪
♪ 依然记得从你口中说出再见 ♪
♪ 坚决如铁 ♪
昏暗中有种烈日灼身的错觉
黄昏的地平线
♪ 划出一句离回 ♪
继续行驶1.5km
进入永夜
♪ 依然记得从你眼中滑落的泪 ♪
伤心欲绝
♪ 混乱中有种热泪烧伤的错觉 ♪
黄昏的地平线
♪ 割断幸福喜悦 ♪
相爱已经幻灭
♪ 生命宛如首歌 ♪
♪ 疲倦还剩下黑眼圈 ♪
红灯即将变绿的世界
♪ 伤害在所难免 ♪
♪ 黄昏再美 ♪
♪ 终要 ♪
♪ 依然记得从你口中说出再见 ♪
♪ 坚决如铁 ♪
♪ 昏暗中有种烈日灼身的错觉 ♪
♪ 黄昏的地平线 ♪
♪ 划出一句离别风 ♪
♪ 轻轻拥有一夜 ♪
♪ 依然记得从你你眼中滑落的泪 ♪
伤心欲绝
万中有种热泪烧伤的错觉
♪ 黄昏的地平线 ♪
♪ 割断幸福喜悦 ♪
♪ 相爱已经幻灭 ♪
过红绿灯后再下个红绿灯右转
♪ 依然记得从你口中说出再见 ♪
♪ 坚决如铁 ♪
♪ 昏暗中有种烈日灼身的错觉 ♪
♪ 黄昏的地平线 ♪
♪ 划出一句离别爱情情如柔 ♪
♪ 依然记得从你眼中滑落的泪 ♪
♪ 伤心欲绝 ♪
♪ 混乱中有种热泪烧伤的错觉 ♪
♪ 黄昏的地平线割断幸福喜悦 ♪
再一次我右转
随后200米左转
200米后左转
你
即将左转
下午好友均价买东朋友
一天吃的不上当
所有人送你会从那遥远海边消失的你
本来模糊明脸
竟然渐渐清晰
♪ 想要说些什么 ♪
♪ 又不知从何说起 ♪
却又把它放在心底
♪ 茫然走在海边 ♪
♪ 看那潮来潮去 ♪
♪ 徒劳无功 ♪
♪ 想把每朵浪花记清 ♪
♪ 想要说声爱你 ♪
♪ 却被吹散在风里猛然回头 ♪
♪ 你在哪里 ♪
♪ 如果大海能够唤回荆棘心的爱 ♪
♪ 就让我用一生等待泪 ♪
♪ 如果深情往事你已不再留恋 ♪
♪ 就让它随风飘 ♪
♪ 如果大海能够带走我的的哀愁 ♪
♪ 就像带走每条河流 ♪
♪ 所有受过的伤 ♪
♪ 所有流过的泪 ♪
♪ 我的爱 ♪
♪ 请全部带走 ♪